than historical IgE therapies, given the ability to target IgE in a fundamentally different way.
In the case of Murex, a novel payload that hopefully has the NMTI payload that has a cleaner
profile than the toposomerase payloads. But I think you have to have some sort of differentiated
conviction just given that the price levels are climbing. You know, that said, you have to be able
to access external innovation to grow companies of our size. So, we have to just keep looking for
that right balance of breakthrough science and then finding the right balance from a valuation
standpoint.
Your point on Palo-Carson is well taken. I mean, there is, you know, an element here of the
MACE endpoint versus, you know, CV death. Lp is associated with high rates of sudden cardiac death,
particularly in younger patients. Very difficult, of course, for us to say without having,
you know, locked the database and seen the data to know exactly. But there is at least the
potential for CV death to be an important component, at least theoretically, given the profile of Lp
and something we'll have to look carefully at and how that drives versus other elements of the endpoint.
Next question.
Thank you. Your next question comes from the line of Kerry Holford from Barenberg. Please go ahead.
Thank you very much. Question for me on Kitsukale, just on the IP. The extension that you've been
granted related to pediatric.
Can you confirm now that that complimentary expiry is May 2032, and in the context of your earlier
settlements of generic players, is that when we should now be assuming generic market?
Thanks for the question. So our guidance is second half 2031. So Q3 2031 guidance for LOE for
Kitsukale with the pediatric service.
pediatric exclusivity. And that's inclusive of the settlements that we have with generic
manufacturers. Thank you. And just as a quick note as well, we double checked. In China for
Cosimta, we have 70% market share and our market leader as well. Next question, Alfred.